The Face Crate #2 is on sale for Juneteenth! [www.brickplanet.com/shop/18202/face-crate-2](https://www.brickplanet.com/shop/18202/face-crate-2)

Privacy Policy

Last Updated: November 8th, 2022

BrickPlanet Inc., or "BrickPlanet" is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those that visit our website and make use of our services accurate, confidential, secure and private. This privacy policy was created and written to show our users and members what type of information we use, collect, and share.

Therefore, this privacy policy agreement shall apply to Brickplanet, Inc. and it's subsidiaries, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of our web site, you are herein consenting to the following data procedures express within this agreement.

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

1.Our web site collects various types of information, such as:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| A.  | Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information ect., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested. |
| B.  | Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, geographical information, third party tracking technologies, and server logs. |

Please rest assured that our web site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is in the intent of our web site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on our web site.

Brickplanet, Inc. may have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information, such as the age or gender of our users. We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address, or type of operating system for informational and logging purposes.

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review this privacy policy frequently as a means to better understand the way in which our web site makes use of and shares information collected.

USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

1.Brickplanet, Inc. may collect and make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our web site and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and services available on our web site. Brickplanet, Inc. may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.2.Brickplanet, Inc. does not now, or will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists, names, and/or information to any third parties.3.Brickplanet, Inc. may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| A.  | Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and /or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Brickplanet, Inc. and/or our web site; |
| B.  | Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Brickplanet, Inc.; and |
| C.  | Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of our web site and/or the general public. |

OPT OUT AND UNSUBSCRIBE

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 1.  | All users and/or members to our web site have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe from our newsletters or emails, please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to [\[email protected\]](https://www.brickplanet.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). |

SECURITY

Brickplanet, Inc. shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control.

Our web site also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build user's trust and confidence in the internet and web site use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 1.  | Brickplanet, Inc. reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes on our website banner so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Brickplanet, Inc. decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. User at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner. |

ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 1.  | Through the use of our web site, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned privacy policy agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our web site. In addition, you continued use of our web site following the posting of any updates or changes to our privacy policy shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes. |

CONTACT INFORMATION

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 1.  | If you have any questions or concerns regarding the privacy policy agreement related to our web site, please feel free to contact us at the following mailing address, email or phone number.<br><br>Email Address:  <br>Brickplanet, Inc.  <br>Attn: Customer Support  <br>[\[email protected\]](https://www.brickplanet.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) |
